<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Oral Care For The Elderly</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="cavitiesHead">Dental Cavities</string>
    <string name="cavitiesInfo">Cavities (or Caries) occur as a result of tooth decay.\n\nTooth decay is the destruction of the tooth structure. Tooth decay can affect both the enamel and the dentin.</string>
    <string name="cavity_pic">cavity_pic</string>
    <string name="New_Activity">New Activity</string>
    <string name="button">Self Care</string>
    <string name="b">Patient Care</string>
    <string name="c">Login</string>
    <string name="d">Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_natural_teeth">Natural Teeth</string>
    <string name="natural_teeth">Natural Teeth</string>
    <string name="denture_care">Denture Care</string>
    <string name="mouth_care">Mouth Care</string>
    <string name="difficulty_with_mouth_opening">Difficulty with Mouth Opening</string>
    <string name="dry_mouth">Dry Mouth</string>
    <string name="why_important">Why Oral Care is Important</string>
    <string name="oral_health">Oral Health</string>
    <string name="dex_issues">Dexterity Issues</string>




    <string name="care4denture">Care for Dentures</string>




    <string name="title_activity_gum_disease_main">Gum Disease</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseSigns">Signs</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseCauses">Causes</string>

    <string name="cavitiesTitle">Cavities</string>
    <string name="plaqueTitle">Plaque</string>

    <string name="title_activity_register">Register</string>
    <string name="empty_string" />
    <string name="title_activity_dry_mouth_remedies">Dry Mouth Remedies</string>
    <string name="oralBalanceData"><![CDATA[Oralbalance©\n\nA long lasting lubricant that relieves, soothes and protects dry mouth tissues against dry discomfort, minor irritations, and burning sensations.]]></string>
    <string name="water_glass">Regular Water\n\nKeep a water bottle handy and take sips frequently.</string>
    <string name="water_info">Keep a water bottle handy and take sips frequently. It\'s also important to stay away from acidic beverages, such as orange juice, soda and any drink that contains citric or phosphoric acid.</string>
    <string name="sweets">Sugar-Free Sweets\n\nSuck on sugar-free hard candies to stimulate the flow of saliva.</string>
    <string name="sweets_info">Suck on sugar-free hard candies to stimulate the flow of saliva.</string>
    <string name="mouthWashHead">Bioxtra Mouthwash (250ml)(BIOX3)</string>
    <string name="mouthWashBullets">● Prolonging the action of BioXtra toothpaste \n● Supplementing saliva\'s natural protective mechanisms \n● Maintaining a pH which helps prevent plaque formation \n● Refreshing and moistening the mouth</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="oralB">Oralbalance© long lasting lubricant relieves, soothes and protects dry mouth tissues against dry discomfort, minor irritations, and burning sensations.</string>
    <string name="newTo">New to DentalTech? Register here</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="username">Username :</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password :</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="image_count">image_count</string>

    <string name="testIMG">testIMG</string>

    <string name="dryMouthHead">Understanding Problems associated with Dry Mouth</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo">● Dry mouth is not a normal part of aging.\n\n● Many common medications reduce the production of saliva.\n\n● Many of the persons you care for are taking these medications and will suffer from dry mouth.\n\n● Dry mouth can increase risk of dental cavities, gum disease and infection.\n\n● Dry mouth can also make it hard to eat, swallow, taste, speak and can cause dentures not to fit properly.</string>
    <string name="drymouthhead">dryMouthHead</string>
    <string name="drymouthinfo">dryMouthInfo</string>

    <string name="gumDiseaseSignsInfo">● Bleeding Gums\n\n● Red, swollen, or tender gums\n\n● Persistent bad breath\n\n● Bad taste in the mouth\n\n● Receding gums\n\n● Formation of deep pockets\n\n● Loose or shifting teeth</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseCausesInfo">► Illnesses may affect the condition of the gums.\n\n► Medications can affect oral health.\n\n► Bad habits such as smoking, make it harder for gum tissue to repair itself.\n\n► Poor oral hygiene habits.\n\n► Family history of dental disease.</string>
    <string name="resident_change_1"> 1. Please email nursinghome@dentaltech.ie\n2. Have in hands Residents full name\n3. Provide either their PPS number or Medical card number so that we can update our records\n4. Let us know which one of the above 4 options apply</string>
    <string name="resident_change_2">1. Please email nursinghome@dentaltech.ie \n2. Have in hands complete medical history form for this new resident \n3. Please include a photo copy of the resident’s medical card \n4. Let us know if there is any specific dental issue that needs immediate attention. \n\nNote: We will endeavour to examine all new but we cannot always guarantee this.</string>
    <string name="resident_damaged">Please wrap the denture up safely with all of the prices. Place in a envelope with the patients name and a photocopy of their medical card or a cheque for €85 if no medical card or invalid/expired medical card. Please call Dental Tech Group on 01 455 1866 and we will collect the denture for repair and return within 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="resident_damaged2">We will need to schedule a visit to take an impression of the patients mouth, Please Call Dental Tech Group on 01 455 1866.</string>
    <string name="resident_damaged3">Please Call Dental Tech Group on 01 455 1866 to discuss. </string>
    <string name="dexMain_head">User Friendly Hygiene Aids</string>
    <string name="elec_brush_head">Electric Toothbrush</string>
    <string name="collis_head">Collis Curve Toothbrush</string>
    <string name="floss_head">Floss Holders</string>
    <string name="interdental_head">Inter Dental Brushes</string>
    <string name="handle_grips_head">Handle Grips</string>
    <string name="three_way_head">Dr Barmans 3-Way Toothbrush</string>

    <string name="dexterityMain">The following are some user friendly hygiene aids that can be of help in cases where there are dexterity issues.</string>
    <string name="elec_brush">Electric toothbrushes have larger handles that can be gripped more easily by persons with physical impairments.\n\nThey are also easier for caregivers to use when cleaning someone else’s teeth.</string>
    <string name="collis">The Collis Curve toothbrush is designed with three rows of bristles that can clean the front, back, and top surfaces of teeth at the same time.\n\nThis brush may be easier for caregivers to use and also for older persons that have limited movement in their fingers and hands.</string>
    <string name="floss">Flossing can be difficult to do even for those of us that don’t have any physical or cognitive impairments.\n\nFor more control you could try holders that come with long handles.\n\nThis dental aid can be very helpful for caregivers.</string>
    <string name="interdental">Inter Dental-brushes are little toothbrushes and come in a variety of sizes.\n\nThese are especially good when there are spaces between teeth.\n\nPiksters are the interdental brushes we recommend as they have a longer handle than other varieties.</string>
    <string name="handle_grips">Two or three of these on a toothbrush can help those with  manual Dexterity issues.</string>
    <string name="three_way">Ideal as, like the collis curve, you can clean font back and top of teeth at the same time.</string>

    <string name="plaqueHead">What is Plaque?</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo1">Plaque is the most common and serious dental health issue.\n\nIt is a soft and sticky film of bacteria from food and sweets.\n\nHardened plaque is called calculus and holds bacteria in the mouth. It causes damage to the gums and bone that supports the teeth.</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo2">It is plaque, not aging, that causes tooth loss!</string>

    <string name="oralcarehead1">Why is Oral Health Important?</string>
    <string name="oralcarehead2">The mouth is a mirror of health and disease</string>
    <string name="oralcarehead3">Importance of Dental Health to Overall Health and Well-Being</string>
    <string name="oralcarehead4">Consequences of\nPoor Oral Health – Psychological</string>
    <string name="oralcarehead5">Consequences of\nPoor Oral Health- Physical</string>
    <string name="oralcarebody1">► Dental health is important because dental disease and mouth problems are common in the nursing home and homebound population.\n\n►You have probably noticed that many of the persons you care for have problems with their mouths.</string>
    <string name="oralcarebody2">The mouth has been called a mirror of health and disease because there you’ll find signs of:\n\n► Systemic diseases\n\n► Nutritional deficiencies</string>
    <string name="oralcarebody3">Oral health and general health should  not  be thought of as being separate.\n\nCommon Conditions seen in many patients:\n\n► Cardiovascular disease\n► Diabetes\n► Malnutrition\n► Stroke\n► Pneumonia\n\nPoor oral health can make these medical problems worse because of the increased bacteria in the mouth that spread to other systems of the body.</string>
    <string name="oralcarebody4">► Poor self-esteem - Decreased social interaction\n\n► Problems with eating, sleeping or speech\n\n► Mouth pain</string>
    <string name="oralcarebody5">The most common mouth problems in patients in long-term care are:\n\n► Gum Disease\n\n► Dental Cavities\n\n► Sores in the Mouth\n\n► Ill-fitting Dentures\n\n► Little Saliva</string>

    <string name="hygieneHead">Denture Hygiene</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo">Dentures must be cleaned at least once daily.\n\nUse a denture brush or soft toothbrush and rub off plaque and food particles on teeth including the outside and inside of denture under running water.\n\nPut a towel in the sink to protect dentures from breaking if they fall accidentally or use a plastic bowl.\n\nDenture cleaning tablets can be used but only AFTER cleaning with washing up liquid and warm (hand hot) water.\n\nAll denture paste or powder should be removed from the denture each day before applying new denture paste or powder.</string>
    <string name="hygiene">Denture Hygiene</string>

    <string name="careDenturesHead">Care for Dentures</string>
    <string name="careDenturesInfo">Dentures, whether full or partial should not be worn all day.\n\nLeave dentures out at least 6 hours per day to allow the gums to breathe - This is usually overnight.\n\nWearing dentures constantly can irritate the gums and harbour bacteria.\n\nDentures that fit poorly can also irritate gums.</string>

    <string name="mouthOpenHead">Mouth Prop</string>
    <string name="mouthOpenInfo">The foam mouth prop was designed for caregivers to use to help keep the mouth open among older persons with cognitive impairment.\n\nThe unique design of the head and handle give greater safety, control, and comfort.\n\nYou can also make a mouth prop by wrapping gauze to a cushion at the end of a tongue depressor.\n\nIt is vital that EXTRA care is taken if using a ‘home made’ prop as the gauze can come loose and could be swallowed.</string>

    <string name="dexhead">dexHead</string>
    <string name="dexinfo">dexInfo</string>

    <string name="cavities">Cavities</string>
    <string name="plaque">Plaque</string>




    <string name="title_activity_resident">Resident</string>
    <string name="title_activity_emergency">Emergency</string>
    <string name="change_in_residents">Change in Residents</string>
    <string name="new_resident">New Resident</string>
    <string name="tvresident">TVResident</string>
    <string name="please_choose_one_of_the_following_options">Please Choose one of the following options:</string>
    <string name="type_of_denture">Choose the type of Denture</string>
    <string name="p_denture">Partial Denture</string>
    <string name="f_denture">Full Denture</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="parts_missing">Are any Teeth or Parts Missing?</string>
    <string name="clean_break">Is there a crack or a clean break?</string>
    <string name="emergency">Emergency</string>
    <string name="lost_denture_statement">Before calling Dental Tech Group, please check the following information so that we can make the necessary arrangements for a replacement denture.</string>
    <string name="lost_denture_questions">1. Is it an upper or a lower denture? \n2. Is it a full or a partial Denture? \n3. How long since they lost the Denture? \n4. Has the patient got a denture in the opposing arch or are they without teeth? \n 5. Is the patient capable of complying with the treatment involved in fitting a new denture? i.e. 4 visits. </string>
    <string name="medical_card">Does the resident have a medical card?</string>
    <string name="medical_card_scheme">Has the resident had a denture made under the medical card scheme in the last 5 years?</string>
    <string name="private_replacement">We will provide the replacement denture privately.</string>
    <string name="call_denture">Please Call Dental Tech Group on 01 455 1866 with the residents Name and above details</string>
    <string name="denture_cover">The denture will be covered by the medical card scheme. We need to send for approval from the HSE for the denture and this can take up to 6 weeks. Treatment cannot start until the approval is received. Treatment will then take six weeks to complete.</string>
    <string name="before_call"><![CDATA[Before calling Dental Tech Group, please check the following information so that we can make an assessment of need and urgency.]]></string>
    <string name="em_q1">1. Is the patient capable of expressing/identifying the source of their pain?</string>
    <string name="em_q2">2. Has the GP been able to identify the source of the pain?</string>
    <string name="em_q3">3. Was the patient kept awake with the pain or becoming agitated?</string>
    <string name="em_q4">4. Do you need to give pain killers? If yes, what have you given and are they effective?</string>
    <string name="em_q5">5. Does the patient have a loose tooth causing discomfort/pain?</string>
    <string name="em_q6">6. Is there soreness being caused by a denture?</string>
    <string name="em_q7">7. Is there any swelling/abscess?</string>
    <string name="em_q8">8. Is there a suspicious lesion?</string>
    <string name="em_q9">9. Is there a sensitive/sharp or broken tooth?</string>
    <string name="em_callout">Please call Dental Tech Group on (01)455 1866 and we will help assess if an emergancy call out is needed</string>
    <string name="google_android_map_api_key"> Map API key </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="Dry_mouth">Dry Mouth Remedies</string>
    <string name="P_care">Patient Care Menu</string>
    <string name="S_care">Self Care Menu</string>
    <string name="information">Useful Information</string>
    <string name="access_token">pk.eyJ1IjoiYXJvbmI5MCIsImEiOiJjajF4ZTdtMHcwMDBrMzJvMTQ2Zjl0MGdrIn0.Op8xU8ku6G1yuawvY_VEvw</string>
    <string name="Contact_page1">Contact us for more information, to book a consultation, to ask any kind of questions you might have or even to chat and let us know what we are doing great and where we need to improve.</string>
    <string name="Contact_page3">Home Care Clinics:\n Talk to Matthew or send an enquiry;\n Phone: 01 4551866\n Email: athome@dentaltech.ie\nOpening hours are\n MON – FRI 8:30 – 17:30</string>
    <string name="Contact_page4">Nursing Home Clinics:\n Talk to Matthew or send an \nenquiry; \nPhone: 01 4551866\n Email: \nnursinghome@dentaltech.ie\nOpening hours are\n MON – FRI 8:30 – 17:30</string>
    <string name="Contact_page5">Corporate Dental:\n Talk to Bevin or send an enquiry;\nPhone: 01 4551866 \nEmail: corporate@dentaltech.ie\nOpening hours are \nMON – FRI 8:30 – 17:30</string>
    <string name="Contact_page2">Denture Clinics:\n Talk to Amy or book in online;\n Phone: 01 4551 866\n Email: clinics@dentaltech.ie \n Opening hours are \nMON – FRI 8:30 – 17:30</string>
    <string name="title_activity_broken__denture">Broken_Denture</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lost__denture">Lost_Denture</string>
    <string name="title_activity_emergancy">Emergancy</string>
    <string name="careForDentures">Caring For Dentures</string>
    <string name="test">test_string_do_not_delete</string>

    <string name="cleanHead1">Cleaning Dentures</string>
    <string name="cleanInfo1">The best way to help reduce the build-up of bacteria and staining is by having a strict daily caring and cleaning routine.\n\nThe following 5 steps will help you take good care of your dentures (#8230)</string>
    <string name="cleanHead2">1. Give them a break!</string>
    <string name="cleanInfo2">Soaking them in a good denture disinfectant can kill 99% percent of denture germs.\n\nWe recommend using Nitradine tablets for soaking as it only takes 15 minutes.\n\nMost denture disinfectants have a mild bleaching agent which overtime can change the colour of your dentures so check your denture cleaner first to make sure it will disinfect them in a short time rather than leaving them overnight.\n\nBUT PLEASE CLEAN THEM FIRST.</string>
    <string name="cleanHead3">2. Clean them daily! </string>
    <string name="cleanInfo3">Brush your dentures with a regular soft-bristled brush or dish brush, use warm water and some washing up liquid, yes washing up liquid.\n\nToothpaste is an abrasive material designed to work best on the enamel of your teeth  so toothpaste can actually damage the surface of your dentures.\n\nAs dentures are a type of plastic they are best cleaned with washing up liquid or soap.</string>
    <string name="cleanHead4">3. Don’t forget your gums!</string>
    <string name="cleanInfo4">Remember to always give your mouth a good rinse when you take out your dentures and then to massage your gums with a washcloth or a soft toothbrush.\n\nUse a pea sized amount of toothpaste on the brush and gently rub around the inside of your cheeks, gums and tongue to stimulate them and help promote a healthy mouth.</string>
    <string name="cleanHead5">4. Handle them with love! </string>
    <string name="cleanInfo5">You should love your denture, it is part of you and it is fragile, make sure you handle them carefully.\n\nWash over a plastic bowl full of water or a folded towel so as to reduce the risk of dropping them in the sink or on the floor.</string>
    <string name="cleanHead6">5. Make sure it fits! </string>
    <string name="cleanInfo6">If your denture is not fitting properly, functioning well or it just doesn’t look great on you, don’t hesitate calling Dental Tech Group (www.dentaltech.ie) to book in for your Free Denture consultation with one of our experienced treatment plan coordinators.</string>
    <string name="thrushInfo">A mild inflammation and redness of the oralmucous membrane that occurs beneath a denture.</string>
    <string name="thrushHead">Denture Thrush</string>
    <string name="cancerInfo1">Pain is usually not a symptom of the disease</string>
    <string name="cancerInfo2">It is important to notice the early signs of oral cancer.\n\n● Swellings\n\n● Red or white patches\n\n● Sores\n\n● Numbness or lumps anywhere</string>
    <string name="gum_disease">Gum Disease</string>

</resources>
