<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Oral Care For The Elderly</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="cavities_title">Dental Cavities</string>
    <string name="cavities_text1">Cavities (or Caries) occur as a result of tooth decay.</string>
    <string name="cavities_text2">Tooth decay is the destruction of the tooth structure. Tooth decay can affect both the enamel and the dentin.</string>
    <string name="cavity_pic">cavity_pic</string>
    <string name="New_Activity">New Activity</string>
    <string name="button">Self Care</string>
    <string name="b">Patient Care</string>
    <string name="c">Login</string>
    <string name="d">Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_natural_teeth">Natural Teeth</string>
    <string name="natural_teeth">Natural Teeth</string>
    <string name="denture_care">Denture Care</string>
    <string name="mouth_care">Mouth Care</string>
    <string name="difficulty_with_mouth_opening">Difficulty with Mouth Opening</string>
    <string name="dry_mouth">Dry Mouth</string>
    <string name="why_important">Why Oral Care is Important</string>
    <string name="oral_health">Oral Health</string>
    <string name="dex_issues">Dexterity Issues</string>
    <string name="title_activity_plaque">Plaque</string>
    <string name="plaque_title">What is Plaque?</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo1">Plaque is the most common and serious dental health issue.</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo2">It is a soft and sticky film of bacteria from food and sweets.</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo3">Hardened plaque is called calculus and holds bacteria in the mouth. It causes damage to the gums and bone that supports the teeth.</string>
    <string name="plaqueInfo4">It is plaque, not aging, that causes tooth loss!</string>
    <string name="hygiene">Denture Hygiene</string>
    <string name="care4denture">Care for Dentures</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hygiene">Hygiene</string>
    <string name="title_activity_care_for_denture">CareForDenture</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo1">Dentures must be cleaned at least once daily.</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo2">Use a denture brush or soft toothbrush and rub off plaque and food particles on teeth including the outside and inside of denture under running water.</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo3">Put a towel in the sink to protect dentures from breaking if they fall accidentally or use a plastic bowl.</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo4">Denture cleaning tablets can be used but only AFTER cleaning with washing up liquid and warm (hand hot) water.</string>
    <string name="hygieneInfo5">All denture paste or powder should be removed from the denture each day before applying new denture paste or powder.</string>
    <string name="careInfo1">Dentures, whether full or partial should not be worn all day.</string>
    <string name="careInfo2">Leave dentures out at least 6 hours per day to allow the gums to breathe - This is usually overnight.</string>
    <string name="careInfo3">Wearing dentures constantly can irritate the gums and harbour bacteria.</string>
    <string name="careInfo4">Dentures that fit poorly can also irritate gums.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gum_disease_main">Gum Disease</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gum_disease_signs">Gum Disease Signs</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseSigns">Signs</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseCauses">Causes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gum_disease_causes">Gum Disease Causes</string>
    <string name="cavitiesTitle">Cavities</string>
    <string name="plaqueTitle">Plaque</string>
    <string name="dryMouthHeader">Understanding Problems associated with Dry Mouth</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo1">● Dry mouth is not a normal part of aging.</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo2">● Many common medications reduce the production of saliva.</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo3">● Many of the persons you care for are taking these medications and will suffer from dry mouth.</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo4">● Dry mouth can increase risk of dental cavities, gum disease and infection.</string>
    <string name="dryMouthInfo5">● Dry mouth can also make it hard to eat, swallow, taste, speak and can cause dentures not to fit properly.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Register</string>
    <string name="empty_string" />
    <string name="title_activity_dry_mouth_remedies">Dry Mouth Remedies</string>
    <string name="oralBalanceData"><![CDATA[Oralbalance©\n\nA long lasting lubricant that relieves, soothes and protects dry mouth tissues against dry discomfort, minor irritations, and burning sensations.]]></string>
    <string name="water_glass">Regular Water\n\nKeep a water bottle handy and take sips frequently.</string>
    <string name="water_info">Keep a water bottle handy and take sips frequently. It\'s also important to stay away from acidic beverages, such as orange juice, soda and any drink that contains citric or phosphoric acid.</string>
    <string name="sweets">Sugar-Free Sweets\n\nSuck on sugar-free hard candies to stimulate the flow of saliva.</string>
    <string name="sweets_info">Suck on sugar-free hard candies to stimulate the flow of saliva.</string>
    <string name="mouthWashHead">Bioxtra Mouthwash (250ml)\n(BIOX3)</string>
    <string name="mouthWashBullets">● Prolonging the action of BioXtra toothpaste \n● Supplementing saliva\'s natural protective mechanisms \n● Maintaining a pH which helps prevent plaque formation \n● Refreshing and moistening the mouth</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="oralB">Oralbalance© long lasting lubricant relieves, soothes and protects dry mouth tissues against dry discomfort, minor irritations, and burning sensations.</string>
    <string name="newTo">New to DentalTech? Register here</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="username">Username :</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password :</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="image_count">image_count</string>
    <string name="drymouthhead">dryMouthHead</string>
    <string name="drymouthinfo">dryMouthInfo</string>
    <string name="testimg">testIMG</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseSignsInfo">● Bleeding Gums\n● Red, swollen, or tender gums\n● Persistent bad breath\n● Bad taste in the mouth\n● Receding gums\n● Formation of deep pockets\n● Loose or shifting teeth</string>
    <string name="gumDiseaseCausesInfo">► Illnesses may affect the condition of the gums.\n► Medications can affect oral health.\n► Bad habits such as smoking, make it harder for gum tissue to repair itself.\n► Poor oral hygiene habits.\n► Family history of dental disease.</string>

    <string name="elec_brush_head">Electric Toothbrush</string>
    <string name="collis_head">Collis Curve Toothbrush</string>
    <string name="floss_head">Floss Holders</string>
    <string name="interdental_head">Inter Dental Brushes</string>
    <string name="handle_grips_head">Handle Grips</string>
    <string name="three_way_head">Dr Barmans 3-Way Toothbrush</string>

    <string name="dexterityMain">Fine motor skill (or dexterity) is the coordination of small muscles, in movements—usually involving the synchronization of hands and fingers—with the eyes.\n\nThe following are some user friendly hygiene aids that can be of help in cases where there are dexterity issues.</string>
    <string name="elec_brush">Electric toothbrushes have larger handles that can be gripped more easily by persons with physical impairments.\n\nThey are also easier for caregivers to use when cleaning someone else’s teeth.</string>
    <string name="collis">The Collis Curve toothbrush is designed with three rows of bristles that can clean the front, back, and top surfaces of teeth at the same time.\n\nThis brush may be easier for caregivers to use and also for older persons that have limited movement in their fingers and hands.</string>
    <string name="floss">Flossing can be difficult to do even for those of us that don’t have any physical or cognitive impairments.\n\nFor more control you could try holders that come with long handles.\n\nThis dental aid can be very helpful for caregivers and among older persons who have dexterity problems.</string>
    <string name="interdental">Inter Dental-brushes are little toothbrushes and come in a variety of sizes.\n\nThese are especially good when there are spaces between teeth.\n\nPiksters are the interdental brushes we recommend as they have a longer handle than other varieties.</string>
    <string name="handle_grips">2 or 3 of these on a toothbrush can help those with  manual Dexterity issues.</string>
    <string name="three_way">Ideal as, like the collis curve, you can clean font back and top of teeth at the same time.</string>

</resources>
